aera.net 2019-06-02

# AERA Privacy Policy

AERA

Privacy Statement

The American Educational Research Association (AERA) is committed to maintaining your confidence and trust, and maintains the following privacy policy to protect personal information you provide online.

Basic Confidentiality Policy  
Where personal information is required for use of the website or in interacting with the website it is AERA policy that information, such as your name, postal and e-mail address or telephone number, is private and confidential. The personal information you provide is stored in a secure location, is accessible only by appropriate staff, and is used only for the purposes for which you provide the information, such as to reply to your request or to send you requested materials. Note: the membership directory is a benefit of membership. The directory’s information is based on that information which members have indicated is publishable and it is available to other members in the Members Only site.

If you also indicate on our site that you would like to receive announcements and notices from AERA, your personal information will be added to the appropriate AERA mailing list. If at any time you change your mind and would like to add or remove your name from AERA's mailing list, or correct your personal information, you may change this information within the Update Your Record portion of the Members Only site. You may also email us at [members@aera.net](mailto:members@aera.net).

No Release of Information to Third Parties  
Personal information collected as a function of this website will not be released to third parties except to further the purpose for which you provide the information or if such release is required by law. Note, the membership directory is available to members in the Members Only site. The directory is compiled from information provided by members for reference uses such as searching for and contacting colleagues or for making referrals, etc.

Identifiable Information  
Our website does not track or collect personal information about visitors except to enable personalized features for the express purpose of the visitor's interaction with the AERA web site. This information is treated in accordance with the Basic Confidentiality Policy. We do not distribute personal information about visitors. We regularly compile aggregate statistics that show the number of visitors to our site, the requests we receive for particular information on our website, and the Internet Service Providers (ISPs) that those requests come from. These aggregated statistics are used by internal AERA technical support staff to improve the website in an ongoing effort to provide better information and services to the public.
